Balina Sujana

Senior Business Analyst& Implementation Specialist

Former Science Faculty Former B.Sc Nurse Staff Contact No.: -9550722179

E-mail:- balinasujana@gmail.com

Present Address

H:No-8-1-284/OU/4/1,Second Floor Near Vet Care Pet Clinic,OU Colony,Shaikpet Hyderabad Pin:50008

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Highly qualified Business Analyst & Implementation Specialist with experience in the Health Care IT Industry. Enjoy creative problem solving and getting exposure on multiple projects, and I would excel in the collaborative environment on which your company prides itself.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Business Analyst and Tester at Deloitte India pvt.Consulting Hyderabad,January 2022 to December 2022

- Creating and implementing both reports and analysis that help maximize the effectiveness of health management initiatives and strategies
 - Testing both source and target databases.
 - Troubleshooting for bugs and errors and finding

solutions for them.

- Working with back-end and database testers.
- Identifying data sources and requirements.
- Identifying bugs and defects before data processing

occurs.

• Analyzing mapping transformations.

Developing ETL test cases. Developing test plans and test scripts, providing analytical expertise to support data quality improvement, and recommending methods to minimize clinical workloads

Senior Business Analyst &Implementation Specialist at Seven-Hills e-Health Pvt.Ltd,Hyderabad,June 2016 to Feb. 2020

- Underwriting, preparing reports, performing healthcare data analysis and data validation, producing requirements gathering and writing functional specifications, performing workflow analysis, acting as liaison between the customer and the technical team, and providing project management support
- Expertise on gathering functional requirements and documents FRS/PRD/BRD and design documents.
- Content writing, proposal documentation and coordination with vendors and clients.
- Identify and reconcile errors in client data to ensure accurate business requirements.
- Organized project implementation resources and leveraged expertise to assist organizational roll-out.
- Evaluated and defined internal and customer needs, implementing processes to address requirements.
- Onsite meetings with clients throughout the project cycle and into support.
- Online & Offline demonstrations, training, and support for new and existing customers on our online ordering platform.
- Focused solutions on industry-specific workflow, client base and protocols, tailoring implementations to client
- Aided senior leadership in authoring data capturing reports to identify issues and determine solutions.
- Responded to support requests from end users and patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Created plans and communicated deadlines to ensure projects were completed on time.
- Daily Onsite Rounds to each & every Department to know the End Users feedback on the process
- Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.
- Developing test plans and test scripts, providing analytical expertise to support data quality improvement, and recommending methods to minimize clinical workloads
- Excel expertise and presentation to leadership.
- Evaluate risk related to requirements implementation, testing processes, project communication, and training saving
- Estimate time frames, quality, and quantity of resources required to successfully implement product
- Oversee appropriate resources assigned to complete project tasks according to plan; establish criteria concerning deliverability, performance, maintenance, design, and costs
- Conduct status checks with clients and team to assess progress against plan; perform re-forecast of project

variables as necessary

- Act as liaison between company and client; able to coordinate internal and vendor technical teams
- Help research and develop documentation materials for education and training users; ensure documentation is technically accurate and conforms to company's style
- Assist with researching, designing, scheduling, and implementing education and training documentation projects; develop project plan for creating/updating courseware

STRENGTH & SKILLS

- Team leadership
- Client training
- Multitasking abilities
- Application support
- Customer service
- Adaptability
- Good Communication
- Confident and Determined
- Project Management
- Risk Analysis
- Ability to cope up with different situations.
- Hard Working

PROJECTS

- HIS Project Implementation & Support at Sunshine Hospital Secunderabad June 2016 to May 2018
- HIS Project Implementation & support at Sunshine Hospital Kukatpally June 2018 to July 2018
- HIS Project Implementation& Support with Clinical Online Documentation as a Mandatory goal at SunshineHospital Gachibowli July 2018-Feb.2020
- Sanofi Project Pharmaceutical module at Deloitte India Consulting Pvt.Ltd.
- Online Clinical Documentation of Patient Data by Doctors of OP,IP,OT,ANASTHESIA

Departments, Nurses, Dietitians, Physiotherapists and all the clinical staff.

- •M-fine Integration with HIS for Mobile App 2020-2021
- Doctor App, Patient App ,MIS App implementation as a part

of Mobile app project in Sunshine and Maxi-cure Hospitals

Hyderabad.Remote Aster Hospital Project for Clinical

Documentation through HIS Module

BMS Module Project at Sunshine Hospitals, Aster, Maxi-cure Hospitals, Hyderabad.

• Sanofi Project Pharmaceutical Report module Deloitte-

India Consulting Pvt.Ltd for countries like

USA, JAPAN, RUSSIA, GERMANY and ITALY from 02-

02-2022 to 30-12-2022.

EDUCATION DETAILS

- Masters Degree in Hospital Administration and Health Care Management 2016 Apollo Institute of Hospital Administration, Hyderabad.
- Bachelor of Science in Nursing 2012 CARE College of Nursing, BANJARAHILLS Hyderabad.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name
Permanent Address
Koyyalagudem

• Date of Birth :- 16thJuly 1990

• Language Known :- English, Telugu, Hindi, Malayalam

• Marital Status :- Married

• Nationality/Religion :- Indian / Hindu

• Interest & Hobbies :- Dance, Event Organization, Craft work, Collection of information on various aspects

DECLARATION

I do hereby declare that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.

DECLARATION

I do hereby declare that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.

Balina Sujana

